Artificial and Ephemera 060
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Buildings - Civic Center, The - Civic Center, The, 1900-1907 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Buildings - District Building (Wilson Building) - District Building (Wilson Building), 1908-07-04 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Buildings - Old Brick Capitol - Old Brick Capitol, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  National Woman's Party
- Buildings - Pentagon, The - Pentagon, The, 1941-1958 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Buildings - Publications - "An Essay on the Heating and Ventilation of Public Buildings, with Special Reference to the Senate and House of Representatives of the United States" by J.L. Smithmeyer, 1886 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Buildings - Capitol, US - Capitol, US, 1928-2006 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Buildings - Capitol, US - Centennial Anniversary, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Buildings - Federation of Women's Clubs - Federation of Women's Clubs, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Buildings - Fellowship Forum, The - Fellowship Forum, The, ca. 1914 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Jackson Hall
- Buildings - House Office Building (Cannon) - House Office Building (Cannon), 1906-1924 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Buildings - James Monroe Building - James Monroe Building, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Buildings - National Victory Memorial Building - National Victory Memorial Building, ca. 1920 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Buildings - Patent Office, US - Patent Office, US, 1869-1879 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  "Report on Reconstruction of United States Patent Office Building From March 12 to November 16, 1879"
- Buildings - Post Office, US - Post Office, US, 1898-1958 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Buildings - Publications - "Washington Album", ca. 1900 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Buildings - Publications - "Washington the Beautiful", 1922 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Buildings - Publications - "Washington the National Capital", 1897 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Buildings - Rhodes Tavern - Rhodes Tavern, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Buildings - Supreme Court, US - Supreme Court, US, 1929-1946 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Buildings - Treasury, US - Treasury, US, 1872-1941 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Buildings - Union Station - Union Station, 1902-1956 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Buildings - Washington Auditorium, The - Washington Auditorium, The, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Buildings - White House, The - White House, The, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Buildings - White House, The - Easter Egg Roll, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  "The White House Easter Egg Roll" by C. L. Arbelbide (signed copy)
- Business - B and M Produce Company - B and M Produce Company (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Business - Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company - Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Company, 1899-1945 (Box 6, Folder 22A)
- Business - Chevy Chase Dairy - Chevy Chase Dairy, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Business - Courant, The - Courant, The, 1893-12-01 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Business - Flour Mills - Flour Mills, ca. 1880 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Business - Funeral Directors/Homes - Funeral Directors/Homes, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 25A)
- Business - Garfinckel, Julius and Company - Garfinckel, Julius and Company, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Business - Garrison, J. N. - Garrison, J. N., 1894-06-07 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Business - Hecht Company, The - Hecht Company, The (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Business - Institute of Industrial Research, The - Institute of Industrial Research, The, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Business - Jenkins, J. T. - Jenkins, J. T., 1916-10-02 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Business - National Capital Pharmacist, The - National Capital Pharmacist, The (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Business - Public Weighmaster - Public Weighmaster, 1893-12-08 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Business - S. Kann Sons Company - S. Kann Sons Company (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Business - Thompson Honor Dairy - Thompson Honor Dairy, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Business - United States Horse and Cattle Food Company - United States Horse and Cattle Food Company, 1894-02-10 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Business - Washington Gas Light Company - Washington Gas Light Company, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Business - Washington Homoeopathic Pharmacy - Washington Homoeopathic Pharmacy, ca. 1900-ca. 1950 (Box 7, Folder 1A)
- Business - Woodward and Lothrop - Woodward and Lothrop, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 1B)
- Business - Woodward and Lothrop - Golden Anniversary, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 1C)
- Business - Woodward and Lothrop - Twenty Year Club, ca. 1938 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Business - Woodward and Lothrop - Washington of the Future, The, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  2 copies
- Calendars - 1921 - 1921 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Calendars - 1930 - 1930 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Calendars - 1941 - 1941 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Calendars - 1984 - 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Calling/Business Cards - Calling/Business Cards - Calling/Business Cards (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Canals - Great Aqueduct of Washington, The - Great Aqueduct of Washington, The, 1864 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Canals - Washington Canal Company - Washington Canal Company, 1820-1824 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Canals - Washington City Canal - Washington City Canal, 1845-1854 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Canals - Washington City Canal - Washington City Canal, 1845-1852 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Canals - Washington City Canal - Washington City Canal, 1902-12-16 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  James Creek Canal
- Cartoons - Cartoons - Cartoons (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Cemeteries - Arlington National - Arlington National, 1925-1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Cemeteries - Arlington National - Interment List, ca. 1965 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Cemeteries - Arlington National - Publications - "Arlington", 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Cemeteries - Arlington National - Publications - "Arlington House, Seat of G. W. P. Custis, ESQ" by Benson J. Lossing from Harper's New Monthly Magazine, 1853-09 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Cemeteries - Arlington National - Publications - "Report on the Re-Burial of the Confederate Dead in Arlington Cemetery" by Charles Broadway Rouss Camp, 1901 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Cemeteries - Arlington National - Publications - "Fame's Eternal Camping Ground: Beautiful Arlington, Burial Place of America's Illustrious Dead" by Enoch A. Chase (Box 7, Folder 20)
  from National Geographic Magazine
- Cemeteries - Arlington National - Publications - "Historic Arlington" by Karl Decker and Angus McSween, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Cemeteries - Congressional Cemetery - Congressional Cemetery, Ca. 1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Cemeteries - Glenwood Cemetery - "Sketch and Dedication of Glenwood Cemetery", 1854-08-01 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Cemeteries - Glenwood Cemetery - Meeting Minutes, 1895 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Cemeteries - Glenwood Cemetery - Reports, 1905-1925 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Cemeteries - Glenwood Cemetery - Rules and Regulations, 1854 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Cemeteries - Glenwood Cemetery - "Twentieth Century Memorial; to Lot Owners of Glenwood Cemetery", 1900 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Cemeteries - Rock Creek Cemetery - Rock Creek Cemetery (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Cemeteries - Rock Creek Cemetery - Adams Memorial (Box 8, Folder 4)
  "Grief" memorial
- Cemeteries - Rock Creek Cemetery - Brochures (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Cemeteries - Rock Creek Cemetery - Publications - "Rock Creek Cemetery", 1933 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Cemeteries - Rock Creek Cemetery - Rules and Regulations, 1872-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Cemeteries - Washington Memorial Park - Washington Memorial Park, 1932-1941 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - of District of Columbia, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Commemorative Medal, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Invitations and Tickets, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Letter to Alexander R. Shepherd (1900-11-24)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Programs, 1900-12-12 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Programs, 1900-12-12 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Programs, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Publications - "Centennial Guide to Washington City and Vicinity, The), 1900 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Publications - "Centennial of the Nation's Capital" by F. W. Fitzpatrick, 1900-12 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  from "The Cosmopolitan" (2 copies)
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Publications - "District of Columbia in its Centennial Year, The" by Henry B. F. Macfarland, 1901-01 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  from "Forum"
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Publications - "Future of the United States and Its Capital, The" by John W. Daniel, 1900-12-12 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  stamped "Cox Gift"
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Publications - "Hundred Years of the District of Columbia, A" by Albert Shaw, 1900-12 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  from "American Monthly Review of Reviews, The"
- Centennial - of District of Columbia - Publications - "Rebuilding of the National Capital, The" by Henry B. F. Macfarland, 1909-09 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  from "American City, The"
- Centennial - of United States - "Centennial Guide to Philadelphia, Baltimore and Washington, with Decription of the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad" by H. A. Miller and Company, 1876 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Charity - Charity - Charity, 1876-1941 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  Contains "Estimates for Departments of Charities and Corrections with a Preliminary Report" (1900)
- Charity - 4th Ward Contrabutions for the Poor - 4th Ward Contrabutions for the Poor (Box 8, Folder 23)
  manuscript
- Charity - Address by W. C. Dodge - "District of Columbia: What Its Citizens Do and Have Done for the National Capitol, Local Institutions and Government, and for the Support of the General Government", 1892-12 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  Delivered at the Annual Meeting of the Associated Charities
- Charity - Catholic Charities - Catholic Charities, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Charity - Community Chest - "Washington Foundation, The: The Modern Plan for Permanet Philanthropy", ca. 1920 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Charity - Good Samaritan House - "A Serious Problem: What are We to do with our Poor Outcasts and Disabled and Unemployed Workmen?", ca. 1896 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Note Gitf of Ms. Katharine G. Colt
- Charity - United Way - United Way, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Charity - Washington Urban League - "Displaced Families: Where Will They Go?" by Margery T. Ware, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Children - Children - "Games of Washington Children", 1888-07 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - Bruen Home - Bruen Home, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - Central Union Mission - Central Union Mission, 1942-1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - Christ Child Society - Christ Child Society, 1953-1962 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - Florence Crittenton Hope and Help Mission - Florence Crittenton Hope and Help Mission (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - Hillcrest, The Washingon City Orphan Asylum - Hillcrest, The Washingon City Orphan Asylum, 1853-1955 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - National Soldier and Sailor's Orphan Home - National Soldier and Sailor's Orphan Home, 1876-12-29 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - Neighborhood House - Neighborhood House, 1903-1928 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - Neighborhood House - May Festival, 1927-1946 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - United States Soldiers' Home - United States Soldiers' Home, 1907-1909 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Children and Convalescent Homes - Washington Home for Foundlings - Washington Home for Foundlings, 1927-01-21 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Churches - All Souls' Unitarian Church - All Souls' Unitarian Church, 1915-12-13 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Churches - Allen Chapel A.M.E. Church - Allen Chapel A.M.E. Church, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Churches - Ames Memorial United Methodist Church - Ames Memorial United Methodist Church, 1985-06-28 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Churches - Baptist - Baptist, 1907-1944 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Churches - Baptist - Publications - "History of the Baptist Institutions of Washington City" by W. Ballantyne, 1867 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Churches - Baptist - Publications - "Minutes of the Thirty-Fifth Annual Meeting of the Columbia Association of Baptist Churches", 1912-11 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Churches - Bethel Pentecostal Tabernack Assemblies of God - Bethel Pentecostal Tabernack Assemblies of God (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Churches - Bibleway Temple, The - Bibleway Temple, The, 1991-02-24 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  Dr. Lucille Banks Robinson Miller; 2 copies
- Churches - Christ Church Washington Parish - Christ Church Washington Parish, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Churches - Church of the Covenant - Church of the Covenant, 1888-1913 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Churches - Church of the Holy City - Church of the Holy City (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Churches - Council of Churches of Greater Washingon - Council of Churches of Greater Washingon, 1996-2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Churches - Downtown Cluster of Congregations, The - Downtown Cluster of Congregations, The, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Churches - Emmanuel Baptist Church - Emmanuel Baptist Church, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Churches - Epiphany Church Home - Epiphany Church Home, 1876-02-04 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Churches - First Baptist Church - First Baptist Church, 1882-1944 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Churches - First Baptist Church - Member's Manual, 1853 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Churches - First Baptist Church - Newsletter, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Churches - First Baptist Church - Programs, 1941-1951 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Churches - First Baptist Church - Sermons, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Churches - First Baptist Church of Deanwood - First Baptist Church of Deanwood, 19821994- (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Churches - First Congragational United Church of Christ - First Congragational United Church of Christ, 1936-1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Churches - First Congragational United Church of Christ - First Church Congregationalist, The, 1942-1955 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Churches - First Congragational United Church of Christ - Gabriel's Horn, 1957-1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Churches - First Congragational United Church of Christ - Gabriel's Horn, 1977-1995 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Churches - First Unitarian Church of Washington - First Unitarian Church of Washington, 1828-1878 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Churches - First United Methodist Church - First United Methodist Church, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Churches - Fourth Presbyterian Church - Fourth Presbyterian Church, 1844-1859 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Churches - Greater Washington Committee for Unitarian Advance - Greater Washington Committee for Unitarian Advance, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Churches - Holy Temple Church of Christ, The - Holy Temple Church of Christ, The (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Churches - Ingram Memorial Congregational Church - Ingram Memorial Congregational Church (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Churches - Lincoln Park United Methodist Church - Lincoln Park United Methodist Church, 1978-1998 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Churches - Mentrotone Baptist Church - Mentrotone Baptist Church, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Churches - Methodist - "Methodist Sesqui-Centennial", 1934-10 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Churches - Methodist Union, The - Methodist Union, The, 1941-1947 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Churches - Metropolitan Memorial United Methodist Church - Metropolitan Memorial United Methodist Church (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Churches - Ministers of All Religious Denominations - "Proceedings of a Called Meeting of Ministers of All Religious Denominations in the District of Columbia, in the First Baptist Church on Thirteenth Street, Monday, April 17, in Reference to the Sore Bereavement Which the Country Has Suffered in the Sudden Decease of Our Beloved Chief Magistrate, Abraham Lincoln", 1865 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Churches - Mount Pleasant Congregational Church - Mount Pleasant Congregational Church, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Churches - Mount Sinai Baptist Church - Mount Sinai Baptist Church, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Churches - Mount Vernon Place Methodist Church - Mount Vernon Place Methodist Church, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Churches - National Cathedral - National Cathedral, 1900-1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Military Memorial Service, 1929-1947 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Publications - "A Message to Millions", 1946 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Publications - "Build the National Cathedral", 1923 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Publications - "Cathedral of SS. Peter and Paul Washington, D.C., The Ascension Day A.D. 1903" (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Publications - "Hand Book of Washington Cathedral", 1911 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Publications - "Revival of Christianity Through the Power of Preaching, The", 1924 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Publications - "The Way of Peace", 1946 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Publications - "Washington Cathedral: A Series of Views Many in Full Color", 1939 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Churches - National Cathedral - Reports, 1930-1935 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Churches - National City Christian Church - National City Christian Church, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Churches - National Presbyterian Church - National Presbyterian Church, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Churches - National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception - National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception, 1931-1959 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Churches - National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception - Salve Regina, 1915-1940 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Churches - New Bethany Baptist Church - New Bethany Baptist Church, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Churches - New Second Baptist Church - New Second Baptist Church, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Churches - Peoples Community Church - Peoples Community Church, 1971-1998 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Churches - Publications - "Photography and the Architecture of Washington's Stonefront Churches" by Perry R. Letson, Jr., 1983-07-22 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Churches - Saints Constantine and Helen Greek Orthodox Church - Saints Constantine and Helen Greek Orthodox Church (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Churches - Salem Baptist Church - Salem Baptist Church, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Churches - Springfield Baptist Church - Springfield Baptist Church, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Churches - St. Andrew's Episcopal Church - St. Andrew's Episcopal Church, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Churches - St. John's Episcopal Church - St. John's Episcopal Church, 1863-1962 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Churches - St. John's Episcopal Church, Georgetown - St. John's Episcopal Church, Georgetown, 1851-1868 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Churches - St. Margaret's - St. Margaret's, 1964-12 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Churches - St. Peter Claver Church - St. Peter Claver Catholic Interracial Friendship House, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Churches - St. Paul's Episcopal Church - St. Paul's Episcopal Church (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Churches - Tabernacle Baptist Church - Tabernacle Baptist Church, 1986-1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Churches - Trinity Episcopal Church - Trinity Episcopal Church, 1897-04-04 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Churches - Unitarian Church of Montgomery County - Unitarian Church of Montgomery County, 1958-05-18 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Churches - Universalist National Memorial Church - Universalist National Memorial Church, 1936-1938 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Churches - Zion Baptist Church of Eastland Gardens - Zion Baptist Church of Eastland Gardens (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Circles and Squares - Dupont Circle - Dupont Circle, 1921 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Circles and Squares - Lafayette Park - "Historic Corner in a Historic City, A" by T. E. Roessle, 1890 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- City Planning - City Planning - City Planning, 1958-1965 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- City Planning - Publications - "D.C. Builds: The Anacostia Waterfront" National Building Museum, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- City Planning - Publications - "L'Enfant's Methods and Features pf His Plan for the Federal City" by William T. Partridge, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- City Planning - Publications - "Planning of Washington, D.C." by Pierre C. de L'Enfant (Box 12, Folder 21)
- City Planning - Publications - "Virginia Portion of the District of Columbia, The: Palisades of the Potomac" by Amos B. Casselman, 1910 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- City Planning - Publications - Washington Planning and Housing Association Newsletter, 1962-1965 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Civil Defense - Insignia - Insignia, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Civil Defense - Maps - Maps (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Civil Defense - Publications - "You and an Air Raid: What You Should Know", 1942 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Civil War - Publications - "An Illinois State Agent in Washington: The Activitoes of Harry Dewitt Cook, 1865-1871" by Robert D. Ochs, 1938-12 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  Appeared in the Journal of Illinois State History
- Civil War - Publications - "Brief History of New York's Famous Seventh Regiment and the Events Surrounding Its March to the Defense of the National Capital, A" by Lt. Col. John F. Carroll, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Civil War - Publications - Centennial Programs, 1959-1965 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Civil War - Publications - Clippings (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Civil War - Publications - "Confederate Veteran" (Box 12, Folder 30)
  Pages 377-380 Only
- Civil War - Publications - "Last Stroke of a Master, The" by Hanry O. Swindler, 1929-11 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  Appeared in American Mercury
- Civil War - Publications - "Memorial of The Survivors of the District of Columbia Volunteers of April 1861", 1892 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Civil War - Publications - "Recollections From a Busy Life" by I. G. Kimball, 1912 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  Pages 77-88 Only
- Civil War - Publications - "Rock Creek Trees, A Civil War Story" By Maude C. Lukens, 1931-01 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  Appeared in American Motorist
- Civil War - Publications - "Seventh Regiment at the Capital, 1861, The (Box 12, Folder 35)
  Pages 71-78 Only
- Civil War - Publications - "Story of the First Defenders: District of Columbia, Pennsylvania, Massachusetts, The" by Comrade Grandville Fernald, 1892 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  2 Copies, damaged
- Civil War - Publications - "Washington in March and April, 1861", 1885-07 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  Appeared in Magazine of American History
- Civil War - Defenses of Washington - Defenses of Washington (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Civil War - First Troops Enlisted for the Defense of the Union - First Troops Enlisted for the Defense of the Union, 1902-1908 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  Manuscript
- Colleges and Universities - Beaux-Arts Institute of Design - Beaux-Arts Institute of Design, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Colleges and Universities - Columbian College - Columbian College, 1826-1894 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  "An Address Deleivered at the Columbian College in the District of Columbia on the Celebration of the National Anniversary, July 4, 1826" by John W. James; "Address of the Hon. Alexander B. Hagner, LL.D. at the Annual Commencement of the Law School of the Columbian University, June 7, 1887; "Natural Laws vs. Political Issues, Alecture Delivered to the Graduating Class of the National Medical College in the SmithsonianLecture-Room, February 21st, 1861 by Dr. J. J. Waring, Professor of Obstetries"
- Colleges and Universities - District of Columbia Teachers College - H.R. 8391: A Bill to Establish a Junior College Division within the District of Columbia Teachers College, 1959-07-27 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Colleges and Universities - Dunbarton College of Holy Cross - Bulletins, 1952-1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Colleges and Universities - Dunbarton College of Holy Cross - Catalogs, 1939-1942 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Colleges and Universities - Dunbarton College of Holy Cross - Miscellanious, 1935-1942 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Colleges and Universities - Fairmont School and Junior College - Fairmont School and Junior College, ca. 1930 (Box 13, Folder 7)